Guide to the Albert Ellis papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Audio Visual Material, 1953-2007
  - Subseries V.1: Audio cassettes, 1966-2007
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Return of Friday Workshop, 2005 October 28)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Self Esteem Sickness Workshop, tape 2, 2005 April 9)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Fri Workshop, 2005 July 1, Paul-needs push to date-depressd, Peter-panicked abt breakup/son)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Primary Practicum, Albert Ellis, 2005 July 8)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Evolution of REBT with Summer Fellows, tape 2, 2005 July 7)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Self Esteem Sickness Workshop, tape 1, 2005 April 9)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Fri Workshop, 2005 April 15, Teresa-critical of others and self, Laverne-fear of new men)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Fri, 2005 November 18 )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (A Call to Reason, Al Ellis and Paul Kurtz, 2005 May 14, tape 2)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Therapy-M.B., 2005 July 13; M.B. 2005 July 6)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (A Call to Reason, Al Ellis and Paul Kurtz, 2005 May 14, tape 1)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Ray, tape one)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Albert Ellis talking to New Jersey class, 2005 November 2, tape 1)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Jeff Sawyer)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Erin Gallagher; Laurie DeCharia)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Ray, tape two)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Fri Workshop, 2006 February 27, Annie, Cardell-unhappy marriage)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 31)
      (Jeff Sawyer; Debbie Fisco)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Fri Workshop, 2002 December 22, 1. Man afraid to pick up women 2. Man afraid to procrastinate and be a loser)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Redesigning Your Personality--Talk & demonstration 1985 November 3)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET--Sauk Valley College, 1972 October 20, Dr. Albert Ellis; RET Demonstrations 1. Young male with test anx. 2. Young male angry at co-worker)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem 1977 March; RET Dem Richmond 1977 March 31, Female who hurt her eye)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems Miami 1980 December 11; Reason Emotion and Addiction S.F. 1984 October 11)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (1. Coping with criticism & unfairness, 2. Live demonstration, 1990 August 12)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Albert Ellis, Creative Encounters plus Demonstration, 1990 January 28)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems. Wesleyan Univ. 1984 September 15)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Radio Interview with Mike Davidson, 2002 December 20)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (AE Interview w/ Michael Shaughness, 2002 February 2)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Blank)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Albert Ellis; Albert Ellis)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET PA & RET DOD; ORBRA 2. 1977 September 9, Obsesv jlsy over MF’s infidelity--handwritten note around tapes: Mrj Cnslg 1977)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (NAPJO & NAPRO 1. 1977 October 6, He hittg her, She self-downg, ¾ of Session; RET group & workshop process 1977 June 2--handwritten note around tapes: Mrj Cnslg 1977)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (NAPJO & NAPRO 3. 1977 November 11, Prog w self-downg & dwget; RET Dems, 1977 October 23--handwritten note around tapes: Mrj Cnslg 1977)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem 1. Too slow orgasm, WH. 1976 December 3, Wash. D.C.; Male w prob meetg females, 1976 November, L.I. RET Dem)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET. Dem 1976 November Male, anx abt client comitg suicide; RET Dem. 1976 November Nashville)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Gloria Title, RET Dem)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (NY Soc Clin Psychols, 1972 February 27, Demonstration)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems, 1972 February 8, Univ. of Penn; RET Dems, 1972 February, Univ. of Penn)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (2. RET Dem. Gloria--Afrd of being atkd at home; LOH MP 3.1980 January 3, How to accept self and get persnl grace)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem. Dallas, 1977 March; Group Dem. Balt., 1977 March)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (2000 June 24, Albert Ellis & cltry sola, Kosto Gianni, 1. Need for control & certainty workshop, 2. Demonstration)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (New Techniques in RET 1976 October; RET Dems--Itvine 1976 October, 1. Woman afrd of H 2.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem.--Cynthia, F, Angry at M-in law 1975 April)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem--Washington, 1977 February 12, Communication; RET & sex & love, Washington, 1977 February12)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems, 1984 December 1, Univ. Bridgeport, Riverside; continued. Albert Ellis)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem, 1977 January 30)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET group Dem., St. Louis, 1976 November, Two groups, FL; RET group dem., St. Louis, 1976 November, Male Ndg W’s affect w & w., LFT, FL, song)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems--Mexico City, 1975 May; RET Dem. Mexico City, 1975 May, 1. Perfect M.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Dem. Forth Worth, 1977 March; RET Dem., 1977 March, F Worth)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem, Female afraid of public perf., Allentown, 1972 November 28; Reason & Emotion, Sex, Love & Marriage, Allentown, 1972 November 28)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Male afraid to take a risk of going abroad for a yr, 1983 February 22)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem., Woman whose principal unduly blocks her, 1984 June 3, NYC; Wesleyan Cont, 1984 September 15, Angry at bf )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem, Male bored when alone, 1976 November; Male angry at traffic cops, 1976 November )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem., Orlando, 1976 March, Female afrd of doing poorly in agro )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem., Anne Church, and A. Ellis--Woman w. short involvements; RET Dems, Chicago, 1975 September, Ke Peiser)(Note in case: Dem. W. Anne Church--Woman w. short involvements, Dem [Ken Peiser] Chicago, 1975 September )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Dem. AASEC, 1975 July 14, Somewhat Noisy Tape; AASEC, 1975 July 14, incomplete, Sex Therapy)(Note on case: Dem. AASEC, 1975 July, Noisy, AASEC, 1975 July, Sex Therapy incomplete)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem. Male who is worried, NYC, 1984 November 5; Correspondence)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Case Presentations, Houston, 1986 June 19, 1. Anxiety plus Dems.; RET Dems)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (LA Dems, 1984 February; continued.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems, 1975 December, 1. Florence S. Angry at H 2. Maurice--panicked at sons’ failures; RET and Marriage Counseling, Rockland Community, 1975 December )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem--Walt--Avoiding job interviews, Wash., 1977 March; RET Dem--Deprsd male, 1977 March)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems 1. Jealous female, 1977 February, Madison, 2. Procrastinating male, Indianapolis, 1977 February; RET Dems)
      (handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems, 1977 March; New Developments, 1977 March)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems, Dallas, 1977 March 9; RET Dems, Dallas, 1977 March 9)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem--Overwt woman, Atlanta, 1977 April; RET Dem--Woman w. difficult son--Atlanta, 1977 April, Nelson Mallary )(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem., Woman anx abt not erning money, 1977 April )(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No supervisions/permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem., Overwt Woman who won’t stop, 1976 October, L.A.; RET Dem w. Male who wants to be mr heterosxl, 1976 October )(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No supervisions/permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems, Patricia (F), Tampa (FL); RET--Williamsburg, 1975 November )(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No supervisions/permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Woman glty abt not workg, 1976 October; RET Dem. SF,1976 October )(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No supervisions/permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem--Male fls he is a hypocrite, Nijmcgen, 1977 February 6)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No supervisions/permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem--Male distrustful of female partners, 1977 February, Washington; TV Interview, 1977 February)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No supervisions/permissions)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem. Young male afraid to look for a better job, Columbus, 1977 January, FL; Univ of Ala., 1976 November, Woman blamg self for not hvg Ph.D., Loud.
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Demonstration, Bergen, 1972 February 23, Student drinkg too much with poor companions; RET Demonstration, 1972 February 23, Bergen, Feelings of Worthlessness)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems., SF, 1984 November 11, 1. F. Overeatg, 2. F Strong; RET Dems, St. L, F, 1985 April 17, Also S.F., F)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems, Tim: Procrastination on Thesis, Nhats, July 30; RET Dems, 1979 July, Xavier Univ., F)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Allentown--RET Dems, 1972 March 30, Mother of Sailer; Rational Approach to Sex)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Dupl., RET Dems, 1. Therese--Self-downing, 1974 September, 2. Wife angry at Husband & his children,1975 January; blank)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Quest Wash, RET Dems, 1972 Quest Dem, Jealous female, 1972 March 15)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems--Charlotte, SC,1975 September 26, Lonelinss, 1. Shithood Ken, 2. Louis; Continued RET Dems, 1975 September, Louis)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      ((FL) RET Dem, Woman anx abt poorly hanging her practice, 1977 February; blank)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Albert Ellis, RET Demonstration, Woman with dire love need,1975 September, L, Dupl.; Albert Ellis, RET Demonstration, Woman guilty about leaving her husband, 1975 September, L, Dupl)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem, 1. Male who procrastinates; RET Dems, 1978 September )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Demonstration, Woman with fear of death, L, Dupl; RET Demonstration, Angry Male, 1974 November, Chicago, Dr. Albert Ellis, L, Dupl)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Mod. Loud., Group Dem., Ev. Sho strong Film, 1973 September 21; RET Dem., AL--Evelyn Freeman’s, 1973 September 20, L.A.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem, 1978 January 15, Male w. overeatg & LFT; continued with Frank Ferrise & Luis Nieves)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems, Grossingers, 1978 August 8; 1. RET Dem. RR., 1978 June, "A Bad Mother" 2. RET Dem. Potsdam)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Chemical Dependency & RET, Univ. Minn., 1976 February; Family Interview, U Minn., 1976 February, E)(handwritten note around tapes: Marriage & Family Dems)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (LHP DO 1. W Downg self for prev. Breakdown, perfectionist; LISAR & LISRD, 2. Showg H & W how they upset themselves, 1975)(handwritten note around tapes: Marriage & Family Dems)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Interview with Mary Reinholz on Women’s legs; RIMJO & RIMJA, 1. Upset abt her lv appr, 1975 December )(handwritten note around tapes: Marriage & Family Dems)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem, VA In-Patient w. Psychotic Depresn, 1976 January 16; Discussion of patient on other side of tape)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem., Woman w. smokg phob, Interview on RET, 1977 November; RET Dem, Woman angry at D, January 17, Ohio Univ.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Talk--Dayton,1972 December 6, Loud, Few 4-L; 1. RET--Talk (continued., 2. RET dem--Woman angry at her son & puttg self down)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (1, Tape Two, 1976 May 9, Dr. Ellis, Full; 2, RET Dem)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Therapy Group, 1977 February 2, George--job perfectionist; continued. Michael--irratnlity of flg in lv)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Tape 1 Lecture & Demonstration--Interpersonal Relations, few four letter, Tape is full, Loud
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Tape 3 Demonstration Ellis)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET #2, 1977 July 9; RET continued., RET Dem--Angry abt lateness, male)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (1977 July 9, RET Dems, 1. Upset by T’s answers, 2. Male socially withdrawn; 1977 July 9, RET Dems, 1. Inefficient fantasizing, Perfectionism abt work)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (DR. ELLIS, RET dems, both sides, Huntsville, Ala, 1977 May 16)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Rochester Dems., 1974 October 16; continued.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem--Sex Impotence, 1974 Duplicate)(handwritten note around tapes: Sex Therapy Dems)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Demonstration, 1975 October, Woman obsessed with sex Albert Ellis, Dupl; Demonstration, 1975 October, Diabetic Woman not following regimen, Albert Ellis, Dupl.)(handwritten note around tapes: Sex Therapy Dems)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (Handwritten note included inside cassette case: RET Dem with Beatrice Jonson--[poor recordg. Very helpful to her] Elysium Field, 1973 September 23, [broken tape]; RET Dem. with Beatrice Johnson, 1973 September, [pr. Recordg; broken tape] )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems--Chicago, 1974 May; RET dems--Chicago,1974 May )(Note on case: RET Dems. Chicago, 1974 May )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems--Olympia, 1978 June; RET Dems continued.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dem., Singles, 1983 October 25, Male hesitant to give up female; TAWST 1. 1984 February 3, Nd for certnty. Hrt palpitas.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 112)
      (RET Dems, LA, 2. jealous people, 1980 February 16; RET Dems, Albuquerque, 1980 February 12, 2. continued, 3. Woman deprsd abt deprsn )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Dupl, 1. Therese, 1974 July, 2. W. angry at H. & children,1975 January; Dupl, Male w. loss of erection, 2. Overweight woman, 1974)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Demonstration, 1972 October 24,, Dallas; continued. Mary A.)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems 1972)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Demonstration, Dallas, 1972 December 10)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems 1972)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Workshop, AAMFC, Dallas, Tex, #3,1972 October 30; continued.)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems 1972)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET--Oasis, Talk & Demonstration, Eve. 1972 October 21, Chicago, YMCA; RET--Oasis, 1972 October 21, Dr. Albert Ellis)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems 1972)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Demonstration continued, Young female who won’t do her T.A. paper; RET Demonstration, 1972 October 21, Chicago--Oasis, Young female, guilty abt not being a good daughter)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems 1972)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem--Indecisive Woman, Delta College, Not Loud.; RET Dems, Delta College, Mich, 1978 April 1, continued. female)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permissions, 1978)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem., Dusseldorf, 1978 July, Woman who is overweight; RET Dems, 1978 July, Cambridge, 1. Female w. fr. Of heights, 2. Male wants to stop smoking)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permissions, 1978)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems, 1978 November )(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permissions, 1978)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem, Bangor, 1978 February; AASECT, 1978 March 5, continued. Sex Therapy)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permissions, 1978)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Discussion of Sex & the Liberated Man--Adelphi, 1977 May 20; RET Dem, Black Woman whose H is nt kpg his promises, 1978 March 5)(handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems, No permissions, 1978)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET & group therapy, 1976 September, Atlanta; Group DEMS, 1976 September )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (How to live w. & without anger, 1976 March 6, Philly; Dem--Married couple, Philly, 1976 March 6, He angry at her insecurity)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems, Germany, 1978 February, 1. Psychol. anx abt a job, 2. Male anx about initeting others; RET Dems continued.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem--Male afraid of demonstratg in public,1979 February, Athens, O.; Interview, Radio & College Newspaper, Athens, O., 1979 February)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem, 1977 October 21)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems., P.R., 1978 June; RET Dems, P.R., 1978 June )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem, Procrastination, 1977 December 4; RET Dem, Singles, Minneap, 1977 December 3)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Demonstrations, Therese, 1. Self-blame, 2. Sex Prob, 1975 January; RET Demonstrations, Woman overweight, 1974 September )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Dupl. RET Dems., 1. Therese self-downg, 1974 September, 2. Wife angry at Husband & his children,1975 January; Dupl, M. loss of erection, 1974 September, 2. Overwt woman--Louise, 1974 September )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Group Dem,1976 September, Atlanta; RET Dem, 1976 September, 1. Hurt & angry at W’s lack of warmth, 2. RET Dem. Woman predictg future flr w men--N.D. Mallary)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems, 1977 September, Ed, Deprsd abt W’s leavg; RET Dem, 1977 September, Self-downg for stayg in relaship, 2. Male angry at W )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (1. RET Dem, Chicago, 1978 September 9, 2. Interview for Radio on RET; RET Dems, Oasis, Chicago, 1978 September 17)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems, 1978 March 11, Towson, Woman whose 13 yr old is stealing; RET Dem, Townson, 1978 March 11, Woman afraid to be alone & raped)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem, Steve, 1977 November 3, Ft. Worth; RET Dem, Female afraid to break her foot sky-diving, 1977 November 3)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems, Real Inst., July 8, 1. Male afraid of flying, 2. Woman who must hv a full life; RET Dems cont, 3. Male who must nt be anx)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Group Dem, Lewisham School, 1975 January, Bob--Anger at son; RET Dem, Lewisham School, 1975 January, George--Alcoholic Binges)(handwritten note inside case: Alcoholic, George: Arkansas 5/75, Milwaukee 6/75, Chicago 9/75, Hartford 9/75, NYC 10/75)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem,1974 September 27, Louise, Overweight; RET Dem, Therese, Kalamazoo, 1974 September, RET Dem., Palatine Ill., 1975 January )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Woman who wants to give up smokg, RET Dem, 1978 March 16; RET Dem, Woman not doing what wd be gd for her, 1978 March)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem, W. with little sex desire, APGA, 1976 April, John Gullo; RET Dem, April 28)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems, Amer Psychiatric Ass, Atlanta, 1978 May 9, A Ellis & Elliot Abrams; RET Dems)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems., Wash, 1978 February, Rose Oliver, Russ Grieger continued.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem, Young female rebellg agnst eatg; Hartford RET workshop continued)(Note on case: Hartford Dems, 1974)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem. with a Psychotic, 1974 November 26; RET Dem., North Shore Hosp, L.I., 1974 November 26, Fr of looking foolish in public)(Note on case: RET Dem. North Shore Hosp, F, Fr of lookg foolish in public, RET Dem. With a Psychotic, 1974 November 26)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET, 1973 November 5, Muskegon, Mich; Muskegon, Mich, RET Dem, Young male with serious tick 1973 November 5; RET, 1973 November 5, Muskegon, Mich., RET Dem-Young male with serious tick, 1973 November 5, OK for Workshop)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem, Singles Workshop, Ray, 1974 December 22; cont)(Note on case: RET Dem. Singles Workshop, 1974 December )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Sex & the Single Person--Dr. Albert Ellis, Communitatians, NYC, 1972 July 30, Talks; RET dems, Amer. Inst. Psyther & Psa, 1974 December 8, NYC. (Note on case: Sex & the Single Person, 1972 July, RET Dems, Inst. Psa. & Psy Ther., 1974 December 8)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (1. RET group dem, 1977 September 24, 2. Couple cnselg dem; Group Dem,1977 September 24)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems--Cleveland, 1975 March 22, Albert Ellis; RET Dems--Cleveland, 1975 March 22, Albert Ellis)(Note on case: RET Dems--Cleveland, 1975 March)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET demonstration, Dr. Albert Ellis, 1973 March, Davenport, Ia.; LOPCA, 1973 September 26, Over-wt, lethargy, self-hatg)(Notes on case: Dr. Albert Ellis, RET demonstration, Davenport, Ia, 1973 March, LOPCA, 1973 September 26, overwt-lethargy-self-hatred; RET Dem. Davenport, Iowa, 1973 March, LOPCA, overwt, lethargy, self-hate, 1973 September )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems, 1977 May 6; RET Dem., Young woman afrd to fc people, Balt, 1977 May 6)(Handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems 1977)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem, 1976 December, NYC, NL, Soc. Worker afrd of psychiatrist; RET Dem, 1976 December, NYC, Anx abt parents hvg a party)(Handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems 1977)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Tampa Workshop, 1972 April 8, Broken Tape)(Handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems 1977)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Anger & RET, Montgomery, 1977 September 16, Loud; Anger (continued., RET Dem, Ill on anniversary of H’s death, Mod. Loud, 1977 September 16)(Handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems 1977)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Ron--wants monogomy, RET Dem; VIRSO, Anx abt anx, 1977 September 9)(Handwritten note around tapes: RET Dems 1977)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dem, 1976 September, Male who no longer last long in inter.)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Group Ther. Dem., 1975 January, Dupl; Dupl, Alc. Male & his binges, DIBS & ReReuenta )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems, 1978 April 30; RET Dem, Barrytown, NY, 1978 April 29)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (Group Ther. Dem, 1978 April, Kansas City; Group Ther. Dems, K.C., 1978 April )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems, Denver, 1978 April, RET Dem, K.C., 1978 April, F. Loud; RET Dems., Denver, 1978 April )
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)
      (RET Dems, Dusseldorf, 1978 July 28, 1. Male, 2. Woman w. fear of dogs; RET Dem cont, 1978 August 8)
    - Audio Cassette: (Box 192)